<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-02-21T18:03:15-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">FishStalkers VIP</title><subtitle>An interdisciplinary team dedicated to using machine learning to connect observed behavior with brain function.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Team Formation</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023/02/19/TeamFormation.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Team Formation" /><published>2023-02-19T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-02-19T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2023/02/19/TeamFormation</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023/02/19/TeamFormation.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/teamform.jpg?raw=true&quot; alt=&quot;teamform.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are looking for a VIP this semester and are interested in the fields of Biology, Computer Science, or Math then look no further. In this project you will work collaboratively with a team of people within your respective fields and learn to tackle problems that arise within this project. This hands-on project will equip you with valuable skills and knowledge, as well as enhance your resume with research experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or concerns regarding this VIP please reach out to bshi42@gatech.edu&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">If you are looking for a VIP this semester and are interested in the fields of Biology, Computer Science, or Math then look no further. In this project you will work collaboratively with a team of people within your respective fields and learn to tackle problems that arise within this project. This hands-on project will equip you with valuable skills and knowledge, as well as enhance your resume with research experience.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Meet Our Team Leaders!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023/02/13/MeetOurTeamLeaders.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Meet Our Team Leaders!" /><published>2023-02-13T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2023-02-13T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2023/02/13/MeetOurTeamLeaders</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023/02/13/MeetOurTeamLeaders.html">&lt;p&gt;Here’s an introduction to the various subteams in the Fishstalkers VIP and the team leaders in charge of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Annelie Minor: Social Behavior Team&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IMG&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Team:&lt;/strong&gt; The Social Behavior Team assists in setting up and maintaining experiments dealing with the fish lab. They also help with data collection for machine learning purposes.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Me:&lt;/strong&gt; I’m a third year biology major from Newtown CT. The main extracurricular I am a part of is the Georgia Tech marching band, where I play cymbals. I’m also part of Kappa Kappa Psi, a band fraternity, and lifeguard at the CRC. A cool fact about me is I have an identical twin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Arushi Aggarwal: Math and CS Education Team&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IMG&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Team:&lt;/strong&gt; The CS, Math, and Education Team aims to focus on the education aspect of the research by creating by promoting and preparing educational materials teaching Math and CS to host conferences. At the end of the semester, we plan to have a conference on campus for graduate students to promote the education of Math and CS. We are currently preparing teaching content such as tutorials with datasets for linear algebra to numpy and pandas. Throughout our semester of research, we will be conducting research retention in order to focus on the most effective teaching strategies for all the sub groups through surveys and insights. This undertaking has allowed us to best understand the most optimal structure for the conference and understanding education in general to improve the performance and learning of the participants.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Me:&lt;/strong&gt; I&apos;m a first year CS student at Tech and I&apos;m really excited to lead a team that aims to promote the research and develop content for promoting education in STEM. I love trying out new things from learning electrical systems as part of Solar Racing to Ballroom Dancing in my free time. I also love all types of outdoor activities, hiking, or the time I went sky diving! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Chinar Dankhara: ML for Video Team&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IMG&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Me:&lt;/strong&gt; Coffee connoisseur. Machine Learning geek. Travel enthusiast. Microwave cultist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Nadimul Bhuyan: Math and CS Education Team&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IMG&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Team:&lt;/strong&gt; I have taken on a co-leadership role for the Math and Computer Science Education Group, with a focus on research retention. My group will fovus on promoting our V.I,P through our website, building our reputation, as well as conducting research on education. Our concentration on research retention focuses on the best methods of teaching and we will be able to determine this through the conference we will be hosting as well as surveys we will be sending out.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Me:&lt;/strong&gt; My hobbies include working out, cooking and hanging out with friends. I like to binge new tv shoes and play soccer. An interesting fact about myself is that I have a vast knowledge of subjects that may seem trivial to others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Adam Bhavnagarwala: ML for Expression Team&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IMG&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Team:&lt;/strong&gt; The goal of ML for expression is to use unsupervised clustering techniques to extract biologically significant expression of behavior using neuronal data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Me:&lt;/strong&gt; Hi! My name is Adam. I am a sophomore here at GT studying cs (Intelligence &amp;amp; People). I am originally from Danbury, CT. I like to play basketball, workout, and watch shows. Some fun facts about me: I have a twin and that I like to sleep.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Here’s an introduction to the various subteams in the Fishstalkers VIP and the team leaders in charge of them.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Welcome to Jekyll!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2023/01/27/welcome-to-jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to Jekyll!" /><published>2023-01-27T10:24:35-05:00</published><updated>2023-01-27T10:24:35-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2023/01/27/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2023/01/27/welcome-to-jekyll.html">&lt;p&gt;You’ll find this post in your &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt;, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll requires blog post files to be named according to the following format:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YEAR-MONTH-DAY-title.MARKUP&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YEAR&lt;/code&gt; is a four-digit number, &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;MONTH&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;DAY&lt;/code&gt; are both two-digit numbers, and &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;MARKUP&lt;/code&gt; is the file extension representing the format used in the file. After that, include the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&apos;Tom&apos;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints &apos;Hi, Tom&apos; to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/docs/home&quot;&gt;Jekyll docs&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;. If you have questions, you can ask them on &lt;a href=&quot;https://talk.jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll Talk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><summary type="html">You’ll find this post in your _posts directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run jekyll serve, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.</summary></entry></feed>